const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'which brand does NOT make snowboard?',
      answers: ['Burton', 'Bataleon', 'Armada', 'Never Summer'],		correctAnswer: 'Armada'
    },
    {
      question: 'Choose a flex that is more preferred for butterring.',
      answers: ['Soft', 'Medium', 'Stiff', 'Very stiff'],
      correctAnswer: 'Soft'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which board profile is considered \'aggressive\'?',
      answers: ['Flat', 'Rocker', 'Camber', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'Camber'
    },
    {
      question: 'If you are a begginer snowboarder, where should you start snowboarding from?',
      answers: ['Green slope', 'Blue slope', 'Black diamond', 'Double black diamond'],
      correctAnswer: 'Green slope'
    },
    {
      question: 'In regard to the flex of the binding, if the binding is \'stiff\', what does it do?',
      answers: ['Responsive of your movement from binding', 'More forgiving landing', 'A board is harder to break', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'Responsive of your movement from binding'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is a \'catch free\' board?',
      answers: ['A board that goes so fast no one can catch up', 'A board that is so hard to stop', 'The edges of the board is bent upward', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'The edges of the board is bent upward',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the move where you jump with the tail of the board?',
      answers: ['Nollie', 'Rodeo', 'Ollie', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'Ollie'
    },
    {
      question: 'When was snowboarding invented?',
      answers: ['1950s', '1960s', '1970s', '1980s'],
      correctAnswer: '1960s'
    },
    {
      question: 'What must you always wear upon snowboarding?',
      answers: ['Helmet', 'Helmet', 'Helmet', 'Helmet'],
      correctAnswer: 'Helmet'
    },
    {
      question: 'How long can you go snowboarding throughout the year?',
      answers: ['1 month', '3 months', '6 months', 'All year long'],
      correctAnswer: 'All year long'
    }
  ];